const numberOfQuestion = [
    {
        questionNumber : 1,
        question: 'An HTML document can contain ',
        correctAnswer:'All the answers are true',
        option:[
            'Attributes',
            'Tags',
            'Raw text',
            'All the answers are true',
        ]
    },
    {
        questionNumber : 2,
        question: 'A page designed in HTML is called ',
        correctAnswer:'Web Page',
        option:[
            'Application',
            'Cover page',
            'Front-end',
            'Web Page',
        ]
    },
    {
        questionNumber : 3,
        question: 'An HTML document is saved with the ____ extension.',
        correctAnswer:'.html',
        option:[
            '.htl',
            '.html',
            '.hml',
            '.htnl',
        ]
    },
    {
        questionNumber : 4,
        question: 'The HTML document contains a root tag called ____',
        correctAnswer:'HTML',
        option:[
            'HEAD',
            'Title',
            'Body',
            'HTML',
        ]
    },{
        questionNumber : 5,
        question: 'If we want to place text around an image, which CSS property should we use?',
        correctAnswer:'float',
        option:[
            'push',
            'float',
            'align',
            'wrap',
        ]
    },
    {
        questionNumber : 6,
        question: 'Can we define the direction of the text via a CSS property?',
        correctAnswer:'No, its not possible.',
        option:[
            'Yes its possible.',
            'No, its not possible.',
            'may be possible.',
            'A true',
        ]
    },{
        questionNumber : 7,
        question: 'Choose the correct HTML tag for a large title.',
        correctAnswer:'H1',
        option:[
            'H1',
            'Heading',
            'Head',
            'H6',
        ]
    },{
        questionNumber : 8,
        question: 'In HTML, Uniform Resource Locator (URL) is used ',
        correctAnswer:'To identify a name or a resource on the Internet.',
        option:[
            'To create a frame document.',
            'To create an image map in a web page.',
            'To customize the image in a web page.',
            'To identify a name or a resource on the Internet.',
        ]
    },{
        questionNumber : 9,
        question: 'CSS is an acronym for ',
        correctAnswer:'Cascading Style Sheet',
        option:[
            'Cascading Style Sheet',
            'Costume Style Sheet',
            'Cascading System Style',
            'None of the above',
        ]
    },{
        questionNumber : 10,
        question: 'Which of the following protocols is not used on the Internet?',
        correctAnswer:'WIRL',
        option:[
            'Gopher',
            'HTTP',
            'WIRL',
            'Telnet',
        ]
    },{
        questionNumber : 11,
        question: 'Which of the following HTML tags will insert a line break?',
        correctAnswer:'br',
        option:[
            'p',
            'break',
            'line',
            'br',
        ]
    },{
        questionNumber : 12,
        question: 'Which of the following tags are related to a table in HTML?',
        correctAnswer:'table tr td',
        option:[
            'table row column',
            'table tr td',
            'table head body',
            'table header footer',
        ]
    },{
        questionNumber : 13,
        question: 'What is the purpose of the tt tag in HTML?',
        correctAnswer:'The tag <tt> is one of the text formatting tags.',
        option:[
            'The tag tt is one of the text formatting tags.',
            'The tag tt is one of the image formatting tags.',
            'The tag tt is one of the table formatting tags.',
            'None of the above',
        ]
    },{
        questionNumber : 14,
        question: 'What is the purpose of HTML forms?',
        correctAnswer:'To collect user input.',
        option:[
            'To display the content of an email.',
            'To display animation effect.',
            'To collect user input.',
            'None of the above',
        ]
    },{
        questionNumber : 15,
        question: 'What is iframe used for in HTML?',
        correctAnswer:'To display a web page within a web page.',
        option:[
            'To display a web page within a web page.',
            'To display a web page with an animation effect.',
            'To display a web page without a browser.',
            'All the answers are true',
        ]
    }
]
